#### Ithaca, NY 14850 | admchrysler@gmail.com | (646) 275-6840

## Summary of Qualifications

Self-motivated and goal-oriented creative professional with over 15 years' experience working with computers, networking equipment, and web development. Military background working with encrypted communications equipment, which required a 'Secret' level security clearance. Educational background in web design and Java programming.

www.admchrysler.com

## Professional Experience

#### Technology Consultant | Cornell University

2013-Present | Ithaca, NY

- Fulfilled online e-shop orders for Technology Connection
- Volume software licensing and support for entire campus
- Handled ordering for all Apple products on campus
- Customer service and sales support via phone and e-mail
- Wordpress theme design Perform skilled fitting of parts, sub-assemblies and related mechanical units.

#### Web designer/developer | Self-Employed

2005-2012 | Martinez, CA

- Met and corresponded with clients to determine client needs for company sites.
- Developed and maintained intranet and internet for company websites utilizing Dreamweaver, Flash, and Photoshop.
- Created corporate web sites, portals, and large-scale web applications.
- Developed and designed new web interfaces, layouts, and site graphics including icons and logos using Illustrator and Photoshop
- Comprehensive technical knowledge of HTML, CSS, PHP, AJAX, MySQL, and Javascript coding.
- Responsible for quality assurance of finished websites including the validation of web forms and links.
- Installed shopping carts for business client websites.
- Created and maintained database driven intranet sites.
- Extensive knowledge of web production, multimedia development and design principles..

### Military Communications Sergeant | United States Army

2003-2007 | Fort Campbell, KY

- Veteran with 5 years proven success in logistical management, IT, and military unit deployments.
- Maintained 'Secret' level security clearance.
- Established secure communications via TROPO satellite, CX cable, CODEM, and line-of-site UHF band frequencies.
- Conducted training seminars on the use of military GPS/GIS equipment with instructional aids created in PowerPoint.
- Appointed as company level COMSEC custodian responsible for distribution and security of classified encryption keys.
- Accountable for over \$11 million worth of highly sensitive secret military communications equipment.
- Implemented large secure networks consisting of VOIP phones, video conferencing displays, laptop computers, and various other devices.
- Basic mechanical repair on motor vehicles.

#### Ithaca, NY 14850 | admchrysler@gmail.com | (646) 275-6840

# Education & Training

#### Diablo Valley College | Pleasant Hill, CA

- Associates in Arts | Art Digital Media / Web Design; 2012
- Certificate | Computer Science Mobile and Enterprise Java Programming; 2012
- Certificate | Computer Science Advanced Java Programming; 2011

#### United States Army | Fort Benning, GA

- Basic Combat Training (2003)
- Multichannel Transmission Operator/Maintainer Echelons Corps and Below (2003)
- Combat Life Saver Medical Course (2004)
- Switching Systems Operator (2005-2006)
- Introduction to Defense Reutilization/Marketing System (2005-2006)
- Defense Hazardous Materials/Waste Handling (2005-2006)
- Defense Basic Preservation and Packing Course (2005-2006)
- Defense Marking for Shipment and Storage (2005-2006)

#### **OCM Boces** | Cortland, NY

Certificate | Commercial Art/Photography; 1998

### Personal Achievements

- Created website as a side project for Army soldiers which brought in over 500,000 unique visitors a month.
- Earned expert marksmanship status on every weapon made available for qualification during my time in the Army.
- Awarded 4 medals and 12 challenge coins from the Army.